(Sheldon:)Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Penny:)Welcome to
Sheldon Cooper Presents Fun With Flags.
Before we get started...
...I'd like to announce the winner of our
"design your own flag" competition...
...but I can't.
The only entry was from GameyGamer75,
I know that was a JPEG of your buttocks.
Now, this week,
we have a very special episode...
(Sheldon:)...where we explore the flags of the popular
entertainment franchise Star Trek.
And to help me, I'm pleased to introduce
Internet personality...
...former star of
Star Trek: The Next Generation...
...and the only guy I know lucky enough
to be immortalized in one-sixteenth scale.
Set phasers to "fun"...
...for my friend Wil Wheaton.
- Hi, thanks for having me. Happy to be here.
- Cut.
- What's wrong?
- Sorry, you were brilliant as always.